one of the most overused phrases i keep hearing is it's not what you say it's how you say it no no
it is also what you say and it's also who's saying it i have become increasingly concerned
with how often i am watching black women or maybe it's just black women bots deeply moved and
responsive to what i call sister girl monologue being delivered by folks who are for what it's
worth a part of the bureaucracy that forgets black women and it is seen as a source of pride so often
because they're in high positions but so often the content of what they're saying actually ends up
being a word salad or in complete incongruence with what they actually are doing that's jasmine
crockett giving this energy when challenged on her actual voting record that's kamala harris
shutting down palestinian protesters when she was complicit in the advancement of a genocide
against palestinians and doing so like how dare you and we surely haven't forgotten i'm speaking now
ma'am you spoke and use your voice to lie and you have put forth false allegations of sexual
violence by palestinians you spoke when you told migrants not to come though you are a part of a
government that has continuously destabilized the region they're from since the monroe doctrine
you've done quite a bit of speaking yes that's police chief pamela smith talking about integrity
and you're a police chief you don't get to that level of policing with integrity but folks are
so starved for representation that seeing them do the black girl sister talk feels like representation
to black women and i want to just really bring us out of that hey they know that that pandering
is what brings you along for the ride however the ride they're bringing you along is one to just
play in your face rarely if ever are they illuminating and enumerating specific policies
that are going to help black women and how they are going to actualize those policies because it's
one thing to say this is what i want to do it's a whole other thing to actually be able to do it
but to bring it back around to dispelling this whole concept of it's not what you say it's how you say
it one it's ableist and that it ignores the fact that many autistic people myself included speak in a
very direct didactic way that folks deem aggressive and assertive and two folks will absolutely tailor
how they say something to distract you from the contents of what's being said don't be fooled
support a real one